Hey, you!
어이, 거기 멈춰
-Show me your face. -My face?
-얼굴 보여줘봐 -제 얼굴이요?
What did you do?
너 잘못한 거라도 있어?
How should I know?
나도 몰라
Show me your face!
얼굴 보여달라고
We got the wrong guy.
잘못 봤나…
"YUITO SUMERAGI SABOTAGED GOVERNMENT FACILITY" 2nd Lieutenant Yuito Sumeragi
(유이토 스메라기 정부 시설 파괴) 유이토 스메라기 소위가
is now being hunted by the government
정부 시설을 파괴하여
for sabotaging a government facility.
현재 정부에서 엄격히 수사 중입니다
We now move on to the next news.
이어서 다음 뉴스입니다
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♫A crime in reality♫
현실의 Crimｅ
♫For Heaven's sake♫
For Heaven's sake
♫Accepts any fake♫
거짓을 받아들여
♫And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♫
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♫Won't take it at all, I get sick♫
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♫A girl looking back♫
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♫Casts the miracle into the instant world♫
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♫Did you lie♫
Did you lie
♫Spit the venom♫
Spit the venom
♫I know why♫
I know why
♫I've found a game of ecstasy♫
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♫Red Criminal gets life♫
Red Criminal gets life
♫I've never been in love♫
I've never been in love
♫Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♫
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♫We will fly♫
We will fly
♫Someday I won't be crying♫
Someday I won't be crying
♫I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♫
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
"JOURNEY TO TOGETSU" That was too harsh.
(토게츠행) 진짜 너무하네
First they put him on a pedestal.
영웅 자리에 올려놓더니
Now they are treating him like a traitor.
이제는 또 반역자 취급을 해?
No, it was odd they made me into a hero.
아니, 영웅 취급하는게 오히려 이상해
But I'm surprised to see you here, Wataru.
그나저나 네가 올줄은 몰랐어, 와타루
Ever since they branded me the traitor,
내가 반역자로 몰리면서
I've been worried you might get caught up in trouble as well.
너한테 피해가지 않을까 걱정했어
I discussed it with Major General Fubuki.
후부키 연대장님과 의논했었어
Should anything happen to you,
너희한테 뭔 일 생기면
I'll escape to the hideout.
난 바로 기지를 떠나기로 말이야
Have you heard anything from Major General Fubuki since?
후부키 연대장님은… 그 뒤로 연락 없어?
At the least, he managed to leave the old OSF hospital.
토벌군병원 구관을 떠나긴 했지만
But I couldn't detect his tracks from any system.
그 뒤로 모든 시스템에서 감지되지 않았어
I hope the government didn't get to him.
정부에 잡혀간 건 아니길 기도해야지
Without Major General Fubuki,
후부키 연대장님이 없었다면
I would have been...
지금쯤 난 아마…
For study purpose of our future plans for the Bell Peppers,
향후 벨 페퍼 대책을 위한 참고 자료가 필요하므로
I think it's necessary to conduct a dissection to extract the brain data.
피험자의 대뇌를 해부해 브레인 데이터를 채취해야 하니
What is it?
왜 그래?
I just remembered something from the hospital.
그게… 병원에서 있었던 일이 생각나서
You were taken to a different place when we were captured.
너 우리랑 다른 곳에 갇혀있었잖아
That scientist said I was a Bell Pepper.
그 연구원이 나한테 벨 페퍼라고 했어
How can that be? You can use your brain power.
뭐야, 넌 초뇌능력 쓸 수 있잖아
I don't know either.
나도 잘 모르겠어
It could also be just a mistake on his end.
뭔가 잘못된 거 아닐까?
But it doesn't sit right with you.
그래도 신경쓰이는 거지?
However, I am more concerned about our future.
하지만 이제부터가 더 걱정이야
Yuito, are you okay with it?
유이토, 진짜 괜찮은거야?
Yeah. Our priority is how to take the next step.
그래, 앞으로 어떻게 할지가 중요해
There is no place for us here in Suoh.
이제는 스오에 있을 수도 없고
I also think Seiran is just as bad a place as Suoh for us.
세이란이든 스오든 다 거기서 거기잖아
So, should we go to Togetsu?
토게츠로 가지 않을래?
It's an autonomous religious region. They are an independent city.
거긴 종교자치구에 독립된 곳이니까
We might obtain information even those in Suoh and Seiran don't know.
스오와 세이란에는 없는 정보를 얻게 될지도 몰라
Togetsu...
토게츠라…
Speaking of which, Karen mentioned it too.
카렌도… 토게츠 얘기를 했었지
I have no idea what he meant by it, though.
하지만 형의 목적을 모르겠어
I remember now.
뭔가 떠올랐어
My uncle once went to Togetsu to close some business deals.
큰아빠가 토게츠에 거래하러 간 적 있어
Did your uncle work for the OSF hospital?
큰아빠라면… 토벌군병원 대표로 가신거야?
What was the business about?
뭘 거래한 거야?
I don't know.
그건 나도 몰라…
If it involved the OSF hospital,
토벌군병원과 관련된 거라면
it's likely linked to the brain power experiment and metamorphosis researches.
초뇌능력 연구나 변이 연구와 연관될 거야
I think Seiran had dealt with them too.
세이란도 그쪽과 연관된 것 같아
Are you sure it's safe to be in Togetsu?
진짜 토게츠에 가도 괜찮은 걸까?
The situation is indeed concerning.
불안하긴 하네
But since the hospital is involved,
하지만 병원과 연관된 거라면
we must go to Togetsu.
반드시 토게츠에 다녀와야겠어
I'm nothing like my father and brother.
난 형과 아빠랑은 달라
I've lived this long without knowing the true nature of this country.
이 나라의 진짜 모습을 모른채 지금까지 살아왔고
There are still secrets I haven't uncovered.
아직도 모르는 일이 많아
Therefore, I seek answers.
그래서 알고 싶어
Even if we have a slim chance of finding a clue,
약간의 단서라도 얻을 수 있다면
I'm willing to go for it.
모두 찾아보고 싶어
The Captain's stance is firm. I'll follow your lead.
소대장이 그런 생각이라면 나도 따라야지
That settles it.
나도 그렇게 생각해
Let's go, we're headed for Togetsu.
가자, 토게츠로
Rather than waiting aimlessly,
묵묵히 기다리는 것보다는
why not search for a way to save Naomi?
나오미를 구할 가능성을 찾는 건 어때?
I heard it. Are you seriously going to Togetsu?
토게츠에 간다고 들었어, 진심이야?
I haven't made up my mind.
아직 결정된 건 아니야
However...
하지만…
I've learned the routes of the trucks entering the facility where they keep Naomi.
하루카를 통해 나오미가 있는 연구시설에 드나드는 트럭에 대해 조사했어
They seemed to have come from Togetsu.
아마도 토게츠에서 온 것 같아
There was no registration record,
정보가 등록되어 있지는 않았지만
but judging by the routes, it's very likely they came from Togestsu.
경로만 보면 틀림없이 토게츠에서 온 거야
So the ingredient used to make the ampoules
앰풀 재료인 사람의 뇌
was supplied by Togetsu.
그 공급지가 바로 토게츠일 거야
Come on, Madam Kyoka. That is ridiculous.
쿄카 누나, 그게 뭔 소리야?
There is no way Togetsu would be involved in this massive operation.
토게츠는 그런 짓을 할 곳이 아니잖아
You once told us you came from Togetsu and were a preacher of the Togetsu Faith.
너도 토게츠 출신이라며? 토게츠교의 전도사이기도 하고
They are just a religious community that worships the moon.
토게츠는 그저 달을 신앙하는 종교단체일 뿐이야
I've never known anyone who was involved in Other experiments.
괴이와 연관된 소식은 들어보지도 못했어
But Togetsu is a place with a long history.
하지만 토게츠의 유구한 역사에
It's not surprising if they have information that we don't know.
우리가 모르는 정보가 있다고 해도 놀랍지 않아
Regarding the research facility, we could ask Karen to save my sister.
연구시설 일이라면 카렌한테 부탁해서 언니를 구하면 돼
At least, I thought that was the plan.
그렇게 생각하긴 하지만
But after contemplating the plan,
자세히 생각해보면
I realized there is much that we don't know yet.
아직 많은 일들에 대한 확신이 없어
You have a point. They used human brains to conduct experiments.
네 말이 맞아, 사람의 뇌로 실험을 하다니
What exactly is Karen thinking?
카렌의 속셈을 도저히 모르겠어
Maybe he's keeping secrets from us too.
아직 우리한테 뭔가 숨기고 있을지도 몰라
The Suoh and Seiran forces' motives are also questionable.
스오와 세이란도 이상하고
Wasting our time siding with Karen who we can't trust
믿기 어려운 카렌 곁에서 시간 낭비하는 건
is not a sound plan.
그다지 좋은 방법이 아니라고 봐
But if we go to Togetsu,
토게츠에 가면…
we might find information vital to save Naomi's life.
나오미를 구할 방법을 얻을 지도 몰라
Kasane, what is your decision?
카사네, 어떻게 할래?
As long as there is a chance to save my sister, I'll go to Togetsu.
나오미를 구할 단서가 하나라도 있다면 토게츠에 가고 싶어
Hold your horses, Kasane.
진짜야? 카사네
You heard Karen back then.
카렌도 말했다시피
If there was a slightest mistake,
약간의 실수라도 있으면
who knows what the people from Seiran would do to you?
세이란 녀석들이 너한테 무슨 짓을 할지 모른다고
Kagero, it seems you don't want us in Togetsu.
카게로는 우리가 토게츠에 가는게 싫은가봐
Would there be problems if we go?
토게츠에 가는데 큰 문제라도 있어?
I think Naomi will be safe.
나오미는 아마 별일 없을 거야
Karen promised to keep that research facility safe.
카렌이 연구시설을 지킬 거라고 했으니
He wouldn't let Seiran meddle with it.
세이란이 마음대로 개입하지는 못할 거야
How can you be so certain?
그걸 어떻게 확신해?
I've known him for a long time.
알고 지낸 세월이 얼마인데
I can be sure about this.
그 정도는 알고도 남지
Haruka, what do you think?
하루카, 어때?
You can count on me to monitor the Seiran forces and the research facility.
세이란과 연구시설을 감시하는 일은 나한테 맡겨
I'll notify you if anything happens.
뭔 일 있으면 바로 연락할게
Thank you. We'll be counting on you.
고마워, 그럼 잘 부탁해
So it's decided.
그럼 결정난 건가?
Seriously...
참나
Sister.
언니
I will find a way to save you.
내가 반드시… 반드시 구해줄게
KAITO
(카이토)
You're awake.
깼어?
I have you to thank for that.
덕분에
You saved me yet again.
또 네가 나를 구한거네
I can't let you die just yet.
넌 아직 죽으면 안되니까
Is it because I was Alice's fiance?
내가… 앨리스의 약혼자라서?
It's because you are the OSF Major General of Suoh.
넌 스오 토벌군의 연대장이니까
I still have use of you.
아직 이용가치가 있어
Is that so?
그래…?
Do you still remember that day?
기억나?
Alice joined the force on a sunny day too.
앨리스가 입대하던 날도 지금처럼 맑았어
Alice was so happy.
앨리스가 많이 좋아했었지
She was happy to have finally caught up to us.
드디어 우리한테 합류했으니까
Honestly, I was worried.
솔직히… 난 많이 걱정됐어
After all, she had a kind heart.
너무 부드러운 여자라서
I doubted if she could ever become a proper soldier.
'군인'이 될 수 있을지가 의문이었어
She was clumsy and often sloppy.
바보같이 덜렁댔었지
You always said that about her. It drove her mad.
네가 늘 그렇게 놀려서 화냈었잖아
But she was never truly upset.
하지만 진심으로 화낸 적은 없었지
I never thought we would lose her that way.
그런 식으로 잃게 될 줄은 몰랐어
Did you think about it?
생각해본 적 있어?
Had Alice retired peacefully,
앨리스가 무사히 제대했다면
what would happen instead?
어땠을까?
It's pointless dwelling on the thought.
그런 일은… 생각해봐도 소용없어
What will happen to me?
난 대체…어떻게 되는걸까…
I've had enough.
그만하고 싶어
I'm so scared. I'm in so much pain.
너무 무섭고 너무 고통스러워
Someone, please save me.
누가… 나 좀 구해줘
Don't cry.
울지 마…
I can be your friend.
내가… 친구가… 되어줄 테니까…
It'll be all right.
괜찮을 거야
Haruka, we've deviated from the patrol route.
하루카, 우리가 순찰 범위를 많이 벗어났는데
How are things on your side?
그쪽 상황은 어때?
They haven't spotted us.
아직은 발견되지 않은 것 같아
I'll continue to provide support from here.
최대한으로 지키고 있을게
Thank you. It's a relief to hear that.
고마워, 많이 안심되네
Our vehicle can't pass through here.
여기부터는 차량 통행이 안돼
It's so cold here.
너… 너무 추워
I've heard the stories. But this place is freezing.
춥다는 소문은 들어봤지만 이정도일 줄이야
I know. It's so cold.
그렇지, 많이 춥지?
Some places are covered in snow all year round.
일년내내 눈 내리는 곳도 있어
Isn't that terrible?
귀찮겠지?
It's so cold...
너무… 너무 추워
We should get moving.
얼른 움직이자
Otherwise, it only gets colder.
아니면 더 추워져
She is right.
하긴 그래
The weather is awful.
날씨가 장난 아니야
We might run into trouble if there is a blizzard.
눈이 더 많이 내리면 위험해질 수도 있어
Give up now, it's not too late to have some hotpot.
지금이라도 포기하면 따뜻하게 지낼 수 있다고
It's so cold.
너… 너무 추워
Kagero, shut it!
카게로, 너무 시끄럽잖아
Do you want to turn back now?
돌아가고 싶지?
Imagine your warm blanket and bed.
따뜻한 이불 속으로 들어가고 싶지?
Be honest with your feelings,
본인의 느낌에 충실하라고
my sweet Shiden.
시덴 동생
-It's so... -Arashi, you're so noisy.
-너무… -아라시, 시끄러워
The three of you, enough with the chitchat.
거기 셋, 언제까지 그러고 있을 거야?
Hey, I'm not with those two.
난 같은 취급하지 말아줘
Flowers actually grow here.
여기에도 꽃이 있어?
Tsugumi would be happy to see them.
츠구미가 보면 좋아하겠네
It's not just flowers,
꽃만 있는게 아니라
there are something weird here.
이상한 것도 있어
Others are frequently found around the snowfield.
설원지대에는 괴이가 늘 출몰하지
But we still don't know where they came from.
어디에서 나타나는 건지 모르지만
So this is the unsolved mystery of the snowfield.
이게 바로 설원지대의 수수께끼인가?
It's no surprise.
하긴
The coldness is enough to freeze any brain.
너무 추워서 다들 얼어붙었네
We've been walking for quite some time.
꽤 먼길을 걸어왔는데
How far are we from Togetsu?
토게츠는 아직이야?
We're almost there.
곧 도착할걸
What kind of city is it?
토게츠는 어떤 도시야?
It's not exactly a city.
정확히 말하면 도시가 아니라
It's actually a structure of the Togetsu Faith.
토게츠교의 시설에 불과해
The freaks there are obsessed with the moon.
달에 미친 괴인들이 득실대는
The place is pretty boring.
아주 우울한 곳이지
It's not right to badmouth the people.
뒷담화는 안좋은 습관이야
Everyone has the freedom of faith.
누구나 신앙의 자유는 있어
That depends on the faith itself.
그래도 뭘 신앙하는 지는 봐야 하잖아
Indeed.
그렇지
Perhaps the place has left you with no pleasant memory, Kagero.
카게로한테는 그곳에 대한 좋은 추억이 없는 걸지도 몰라
So you might need some time to understand the people.
그러니까 시간을 들여 이해해야지
Understand, you said...
이해라…
It's a snowstorm.
진짜 눈보라가 휘몰아쳐
Haruka, how is the weather in this area?
하루카, 여기 날씨 알려줘
This is odd.
이상한데
The data show it's a sunny day.
자료상으로는 맑음이야
What is going on here?
어떻게 된거야?
That's...
저건…
There's something over there.
저기에 뭔가 있어
What is that?
저건 뭐야?
Kyoka!
쿄카
-An ice Other. -I've never seen one before.
-냉동 괴이 -이런 건 처음 봐
Give me a break.
이런
This opened my eyes to the possibility of Other variants.
괴이에 대한 인식이 또 늘었어
An Ice Other.
냉동 괴이라…
The snowstorm stopped.
눈보라가 멈췄어
So the snowstorm was its doing.
방금전 눈보라는 괴이 때문이었어
What are the Others?
괴이가 대체 뭘까?
Who knows?
그거야 모르지
Perhaps they are the result of desperate evolutions.
진화한 후의 말로인가
The OSF only told us the Others came from the Extinction Belt.
토벌군도 그냥 괴이는 단절의 띠에서 내려온 거라고 했어
That was all we know about them.
그외에는 아무것도 모르지
Indeed.
그러게…
Look.
봐봐
The silence gives me the creep.
이상하리만큼 조용해
You're right. I don't sense any human presence.
그러게, 사람의 기운이 안 느껴져
Sorry.
미안한데
But I'm not going any further.
난 들어가지 않을래
Meeting the people from Togetsu
토게츠 녀석들은
is no fun at all.
너무 재미없어
Well, that's it.
뭐, 그냥 그렇다고
Hey!
어이, 잠깐만
What's wrong with him?
왜 저러는 거야?
Lady Kasane, welcome back.
카사네 님, 환영합니다
Lady Kasane, you are our precious.
카사네 님은 귀한 분이신데
We apologize for the tardiness.
오래 기다리게 해드렸네요
You know me.
저를 아세요?
I am your "precious?"
제가… 귀한 분이라고요…?
Kasane, do you understand what it's about?
카사네, 짐작가는 거라도 있어?
No idea.
아니
I've never met the Togetsu Faith.
토게츠교는 난생 처음이야
It's such a shame that you don't remember.
아쉽게도 기억하지 못하시네요
But Lady Kasane, you were one of us.
카사네 님은 본래 토게츠인이었답니다
I came from Togetsu?
제가 토게츠인이라고요?
Yes.
그렇습니다
Lady Kasane, you were born with powerful brain power.
카사네 님은 태어나실 때부터 아주 강한 초뇌능력을 타고 나셨죠
The New Himuka Government wanted your strength,
뉴히무카 정부에서 그 능력을 크게 샀고
so they kidnapped you.
카사네 님을 납치했답니다
Nonsense.
말도 안돼
My parents were killed by Others when I was a child.
부모님은 내가 어릴 때 괴이에 의해 사망했어
The Randall family took me in.
그리고 난 랜들 가문에 입양되었지
But the people of Togetsu have never
하지만 저희 토게츠인들은
forgotten you, Lady Kasane.
카사네 님을 잊은 적 없습니다
I've never met you.
접점이라곤 하나도 없네요
But I have questions for you.
물어볼 것이 있어요
What is your connection with the Other research facility?
괴이 연구시설과 무슨 연관이 있는거죠?
We are obligated to tell you the truth.
저희는 카사네 님께 전달할 필요가 있습니다
Lady Kasane, you are our only ally.
하지만 저희 편은 카사네 님 뿐입니다
Now, would you please come with us?
죄송하지만 저희와 함께 다른 곳으로 이동하시죠
I refuse.
거절할게요
I'll tell my friends eventually.
어차피 결국은 친구들과 공유할 거에요
It makes no difference to tell me right here.
그러니까 이 자리에서 얘기해주시죠
Then we must apologize.
그렇다면 어쩔 수 없겠군요
We must resort to violence.
무력을 행사하도록 하겠습니다
What's wrong with them?
이 사람들 뭐하는 짓이야?
It seems they are serious.
진심인가 본데?
Shiden!
시덴
We are outnumbered.
사람이 너무 많아…
Let them go.
당장 풀어줘
Kyoka?
쿄카…?
What is going on?
어떻게 된 거야?
Kasane!
카사네
Now we have the brain that controls the Red Strings.
이제 레드 스트링스를 조종할 수 있는 대뇌를 얻었어
The other one is on his way here.
아직 한명 더 이곳으로 오고 있어
Sorry, Kasane.
미안해, 카사네…
So this is Togetsu.
여기가 바로 토게츠군
It's even more isolated than the rumors.
듣던 것보다 더 썰렁하네
Welcome.
오셨다
Master Yuito is here.
유이토 님께서 오셨어
We came to welcome you.
마중하러 나왔습니다
Well, nice to meet you.
저기… 안녕하세요
Lady Hanabi Ichijo.
하나비 이치조 님
Your uncle has taken great care of us.
큰 아버님의 보살핌을 많이 받았습니다
Yes, but I could say the same for you.
아, 보살핌은 저희가 받았는걸요
You welcome us despite our sudden visit.
갑작스런 방문에 이렇게 마중까지 나오시다니
I appreciate it.
진심으로 고맙습니다
But we should...
저기… 저희는…
You must be interested in the knowledge we possess.
저희가 갖고 있는 지식이 궁금한 거죠?
Yes.
네
You are our special guests.
여러분은 특별한 손님입니다
You will probably find what you seek here.
이곳에서 원하는 걸 얻어가실 수 있을 겁니다
Please come with me.
자, 이쪽으로 오시죠
The moon will protect you.
달이 여러분을 지켜드릴 겁니다
♫I don't need to let fate dictate me♫
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♫Because I believe that I can rewrite it♫
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♫I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♫
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♫Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♫
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♫What's waiting for us at the world's end♫
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going♫
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♫Who can shake us♫
누가 우리를 위협해
♫Who can define us♫
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♫It's nothing less than our story♫
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♫Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♫
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
THE MOON'S SECRETS
(달의 비밀)